Henry A. Kissinger Papers, Part III: Guide to the Yale University Library Collection
Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1941 - 2009; Series I
  - Washington, DC office
    - 2004
      - Cordesman, Anthony, 2004 November-December (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Da, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - De-Dj, 2003 - 2004 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Do-Dy [includes photograph], 2004 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - E, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Fa-Fo, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Fr-Fu, 2003 - 2004 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Ga-Gl, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Gn-Go, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Gr-Gy, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Ha, 1987; 2004 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - He-Hi, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Ho, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Hu-Hy, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Hamre, John J., 2004 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Helfet, David, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - I, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - J, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Ka-Kh, 2003 - 2004 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Ki-Kn [includes photograph], 2004 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Ko, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Kr-Ky, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Lab-Lam, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Lan-Laz, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Le, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Li-Lu, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Ma-Mb, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Mc, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Mh-Mo, 2003 - 2004 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Mu-My, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Na-Ni, 2003 - 2004 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - No-Ny, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - O, 2003 - 2004 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Pa, 2003 - 2004 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Pe-Pi, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Pod-Pou, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Pow-Put, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Q, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Ra, 2003 - 2004 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Red-Rod, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Rog-Roy, 2003 - 2004 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Ru, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Rumsfeld, Donald, 2003 December-2004 March (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Rumsfeld, Donald, 2004 April-October (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Sa, 2003 - 2004 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Sc-Se, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Sh-Sm, 2003 - 2004 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Sn-So, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Sp-Sw, 2003 - 2004 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Simpson, Dan, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Ta, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Te-Tu, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - U, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - V, 2003 - 2004 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Wa, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - We-Wi, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Wo-Wr, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Walesa, Lech, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - X, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Y-Z, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - 2005
      - Ab-Al, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Am-Ay, 2004 - 2005 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Ba-Be, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Bi-Bo, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Br, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Bu [includes photograph], 2005 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Ca-Ci, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Cl-Cu, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Caspian Information Center, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Da, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - De-Di, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Do-Du, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - De Borchgrave, Arnaud, 2005 February-June (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - De Borchgrave, Arnaud, 2005 July-October (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - E, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - F, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Ga, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Ge-Gl, 2004 - 2005 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Go-Gu, 2004 - 2005 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Haa-Hal, 2004 - 2005 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Ham-Hay, 2004 - 2005 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - He, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Hi-Ho, 2004 - 2005 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Hu, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - I, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - J, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Ka-Ke, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Ki-Ko, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Kr-Ku, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - La, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Le-Li, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Ll-Ly, 2004 - 2005 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Ma, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Mc-Mh, 2004 - 2005 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Mi-Mu, 2005 - 2006 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Na-Ne, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Ni-Ny, 2004 - 2005 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - O, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - P, 2004 - 2005 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Q, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Ra-Rh, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Ri, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Roa-Ros, 2004 - 2005 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Rot-Roy, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Ru-Ry, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Sa, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Scha-Schm, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Schn-Schw, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Sco-Scr, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Se, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Sh-Si [includes photograph], 2004 - 2005 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Sk-Sp, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - St-Sy, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Simpson, Dan, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - T, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - U, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - V, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Wa [includes photograph], 2005 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - We-Wh, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Wi-Wy, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - X, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Y, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Z, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - 2006
      - Ab, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Ac-Al, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Am-An, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Ar, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - As-Ay, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Ba, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Be-Bh, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Bi-Bm, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Bo, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Br [includes photograph], 2006 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Bu, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Ca, 2005 - 2006 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Ce, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Ch-Ci, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Cl, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Co, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Cr-Cz, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Cordesman, Anthony, 2006 January-May (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Cordesman, Anthony, 2006 June-November (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Da, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - De, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Di, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Do-Du, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - De Borchgrave, Arnaud, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Ed-En, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Ep-Ez, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Fa-Fl, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Fo, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Fr, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Ga, 2005 - 2006 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Ge-Gf, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Gi-Gl, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Go, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Gr, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Gu-Gy, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Ha, 2005 - 2006 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - He-Hj, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Ho-Hu, 2005 - 2006 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Hamre, John J., 2006 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - I, 2005 - 2006 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - J, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Ka-Kh, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Ki-Kl, 1982; 2003 - 2006 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Ko-Ku, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Kaplan, Robert, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - La-Le, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Li-Lu, 2005 - 2006 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Mac-Mal, 2005 - 2006 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Man-Mat, 2005 - 2006 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Mc, 2005 - 2006 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Me-Mi, 2005 - 2006 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Mo-Mu, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - N, 2005 - 2006 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - O, 2004 - 2006 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - P, 2005 - 2006 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Q, 2005 - 2006 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Ra, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Re-Rh, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Ri, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Ro-Ry, 2005 - 2006 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Sa, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Sc, 2005 - 2006 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Se-Sh, 2005 - 2006 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Si-Sn, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - So-Sp, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - St, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Su-Sz, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Simpson, Dan, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - T, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - U, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Va-Ve, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Vi-Vo, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Wa, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - We, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Wh-Wy, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Wells, Christopher, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Y, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Z, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - New York office
    - 2002
      - Aa-Ad, 2001 - 2002 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Ae-Ah, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Ai-Aj, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Alb-Alg, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Alh-Alt, 2001 - 2002 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Ama-Amb, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - America, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - American A, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - American C-E [includes photographs], 2002 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - American F, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - American H-U, 2001 - 2002 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Americas, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - An, 2000 - 2002 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Ap, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Ara-Arg, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Ark-Ars, 2002 - 2003 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Asa-Asp, 2001 - 2002 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Asq-Att, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Au-Az, 2002 - 2003 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Advisory Council on International Affairs (AIV), 2002 January-June (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Advisory Council on International Affairs (AIV), 2002 October-December (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Bac-Ban, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Bara-Baro, 2001 - 2002 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Barr-Base, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Bass-Baue, 2002 - 2003 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Bea-Ben, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Ber-Bet, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Bh, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Bi, 2001 - 2002 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Bl [includes photograph], 2002 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Bob-Bou [includes photograph], 2002 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Boy, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Bra, 2001 - 2002 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Bre-Bri [includes photographs], 2002 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Bro-Brz, 2001 - 2002 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Buc-Buk, 2001 - 2002 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Bul-Bur, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Bus-Byr, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - BBC, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Blackwill, Robert D., 2002 January-May (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Blackwill, Robert D., 2002 June 3-6 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Blackwill, Robert D., 2002 June 7-29 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Blackwill, Robert D., 2002 July-October (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Cab-Cal, 2001 - 2002 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Cam-Can, 2001 - 2002 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Capr-Caro, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Carr [includes photographs], 2002 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Cart-Cass [includes photograph], 2001 - 2003 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Cat-Cel, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Center for C-Center for S, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Center for T, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Centr-Cerja, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Cha, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Che, 2001 - 2002 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Chi [includes photograph], 2001 - 2002 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Cho-Civ, 2001 - 2002 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Cl-Cn [includes photographs], 1999 - 2002 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Coa-Col [includes photograph], 2001 - 2002 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Com-Con, 2002 - 2003 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Coo-Cox, 2001 - 2003 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Cra-Cro, 2001 - 2002 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Cru-Cze, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - China [1 of 4], 1972 - 1982; 2000 - 2002 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - China [2 of 4], 1972 - 1982; 2000 - 2002 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - China [3 of 4], 1972 - 1982; 2000 - 2002 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - China [4 of 4], 1972 - 1982; 2000 - 2002 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Dai-Dan, 2002 - 2004 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Das-Dav, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Dea-Dep, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Der-Dhu [includes photographs], 2001 - 2002 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Dia-Dik, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Dil-Dna, 2001 - 2002 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Dob-Dou, 2001 - 2002 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Dow-Dub, 2001 - 2003 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Duc-Dwe, 1991 - 2002 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Dilenschneider, Robert L., 2002 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Ea-Ei, 2001 - 2003 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Ek-Em, 2002 - 2003 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - En-Er, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Es-Ey, 2000 - 2003 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Fa, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Fe, 2001 - 2002 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Fia-Fin, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Fir-Fis, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Fla-Foo, 2001 - 2002 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - For, 2002 - 2003 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Fou-Fox, 2000 - 2002 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Fpr-Fre, 2000 - 2002 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Fri, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Fro-Fus, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Fox News, 2001 - 2002 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Gad-Gar, 1982; 2002 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Gas-Gay, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Ged-Geo, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Ger-Gey, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Ghe-Gil, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Gin, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Gio-Giu, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Gl, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Goe-Goo, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Gor-Gov, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Gra, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Gre-Gri, 2001 - 2002 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Gro-Gyl, 2001 - 2003 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Gaynor, Mitchell L., 2001 - 2002 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Global Impact News Alerts (GINA), 2002 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Haa-Haf, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Hai-Han, 1999 - 2002 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Haqu-Hars, 1997 - 2002 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Harv-Haus, 2001 - 2002 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Hb-He, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Hea-Hel, 2001 - 2002 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Hep-Hes, 2001 - 2002 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Hia-Hid, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Hil-His, 2000 - 2002 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Ho, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Hof-Hoh, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Hol-Hos [includes photographs], 2001 - 2004 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Hot-Hox, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Hs-Hu, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Hub-Hum, 1979; 2002 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Hun-Hyl, 2001 - 2003 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Hagel, Chuck, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Ide-Inn, 2002 - 2003 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Ins, 2001 - 2002 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Inter-American D-E, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - International A-P, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - International R-W, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Inv, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Ip, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Ira-Ish, 2001 - 2002 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Ist-Iwa, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - India, 2001 - 2002 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Indonesia, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - International Crisis Group (ICG) [1 of 3], 2002 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - International Crisis Group (ICG) [2 of 3], 2002 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - International Crisis Group (ICG) [3 of 3], 2002 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - Israel, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Jac-Jap, 2000 - 2002 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Jaq-Jew, 1979; 1989; 2002 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Ji-Jk, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Jof-Joi, 2001 - 2002 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Jon-Juv, 1999 - 2002 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Kag-Kal, 2002 - 2003 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Kam-Kap, 1988 - 2003 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Kar-Kaw, 1992 - 2002 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Kea-Kem, 1979; 2001 - 2002 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Ken-Khu, 1989 - 2002 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Ki, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Kl-Kn, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Koc-Koo, 1998 - 2002 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Kor, 2001 - 2003 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Kr-Ky, 2000 - 2003 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Koch, Ed [1 of 2], 1994 - 2002 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Koch, Ed [2 of 2], 1994 - 2002 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Lac-Lam, 2001 - 2002 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Lan-Lar, 1976, 2000-2002; 2000 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Las-Laz, 2001 - 2002 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Lea-Leh [includes photographs], 2001 - 2002 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Lei-Lew [includes photographs], 2001 - 2002 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Li, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Lib-Lis, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Lit-Liu, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - Ll-Ly, 2001 - 2002 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - Mab-Mal, 2001 - 2002 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Man, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Mar, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Mas-May [includes photographs], 2002 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Mc, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Md, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Mea-Meh, 1982, 2002; 2002 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Mel-Mer, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Mes-Mey, 1970; 2002 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Mgm-Mit, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Mo, 2001 - 2002 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Mtv-Mur, 2002 - 2003 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Mus-Mya, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Markle Foundation, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Masin, Michael, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Nak-Nas, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - National A-B, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - National C-W, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Nav-Ndr, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Neb-Neu, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - New A-M, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - New York A-O, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - New York P-W, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - New Yorke, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - News [includes photographs], 2002 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Ni, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - No-Nz, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Ney, Edward N. and Judy, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Oa-Ok, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Ol, 2001 - 2002 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Om-Or, 2001 - 2002 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Os-Ox, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Pac-Pah [includes photograph], 2002 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Pak-Pan, 2001 - 2002 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Pap-Paw, 2001 - 2002 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Pea-Per, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Pet-Pho, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Pi-Pl, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Po, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Pra-Pre, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Pri-Pry, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Pu-Py, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Powell, Colin, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Project for the New American Century (PNAC), 2002 January-July (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Project for the New American Century (PNAC), 2002 August-December (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - Q, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - Rab-Rao, 2001 - 2002 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Ras-Rei, 2000 - 2002 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Rem-Rho, 2001 - 2002 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Ri, 2002 - 2003 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Roac-Roch, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Rockefeller C-U, 2001 - 2003 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Rocket-Ronald, 1948, 2001-2003; 2001 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Roo, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Rop-Rot, 1987, 2001-2002; 2001 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Rou-Rut, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Rice, Condoleezza, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Root and Branch Association, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Rumsfeld, Donald, 2001 - 2002 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Russia, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Sac-Sam, 2000 - 2002 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - San-Sax, 2001 - 2002 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Scha-Schm, 2001 - 2002 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Schn-Schw, 2001 - 2002 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Sci-Scu, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - Sea-Set, 2001 - 2002 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - Sev-Shu, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Sic-Sil, 2001 - 2002 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Sim-Six, 1999 - 2002 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Sk-Sn, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Sob-Sol, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Som-Srd, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - Stac-Stel, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Ster-Stoh, 2001 - 2002 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Stol-Stor, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - Str, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - Stu-Syn, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Schmidt, Helmut, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Schmidt, Helmut, 2001 - 2002 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Shultz, George, 2001 - 2002 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Simon & Schuster, 2001 - 2003 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Taf-Tan, 2001 - 2002 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Tao-Tat, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Tau-Tdk, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Tea-Tei, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Tela-Telh, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Tell-Tene, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Th, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Ti-Tr, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Ts-Ty, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Trireme Partners, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Ucc-Una, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - United A-W, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Univ-Urug, 2002 - 2003 (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - Us, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - USA Swimming, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - Vaj-Val, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - Vana-Vand, 2001 - 2002 (Box 60, Folder 11)
      - Vanh-Vete, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Vi, 1972, 2001-2002; 2001 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Vl-Vv [includes photograph], 2002 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Wad-Wam, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Wan-Wat, 2000 - 2002 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - We, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Web-Wei, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Wel-Wes, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Wh, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Wi, 1977, 2002; 2002 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Wm, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Wol-Woo, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Wor-Wow [includes photograph], 2002 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Wr-Wy, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Weymouth, Lally [includes photograph], 2002 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Wolfowitz, Paul, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - World Economic Forum [1 of 3], 2002 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - World Economic Forum [2 of 3], 2002 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - World Economic Forum [3 of 3], 2002 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - X, 2000 - 2002 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - Ya-Yo, 2001 - 2002 (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - Yu, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Za-Zi, 2001 - 2002 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Zo-Zu [includes photograph], 2002 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Zakaria, Fareed, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Zogby International, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Unidentified, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - 2003
      - Ab-Ac, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Ad, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - Ag-Ai, 2002 - 2003 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - Aj-Al, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - Ama-Amb, 2002 - 2003 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - America C-I, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - American Ac, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - American As-Is, 2002 - 2003 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - American J-Americas, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - An-Ap, 2002 - 2003 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Ar, 2002 - 2003 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Asa-Asi, 1970; 2003 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Asp-Ass, 2002 - 2003 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - Au-Az, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Ailes, Roger, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - American Enterprise Institute (AEI), 2002 - 2003 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Altantic Partnership, 2002 - 2003 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Atlantik-Brücke e.V., 2003 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Attali, Jacques, 2003 March-August (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Attali, Jacques, 2003 September-December (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Bab-Bal, 2002 - 2003 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Ban-Bar, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - Bas, 2002 - 2003 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Bat-Bbc, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Bea-Ben, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Ber-Bey, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Bha-Bie, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Big-Bli, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Blo-Blu, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Bmc-Boo, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 8)